Guide to the Vassar College Facilities Operations Records, 1800s-2021 (bulk 1908-1999)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series I. Administrative Files, 1879-2011
  - [College Center] College Center Borings, 1972 (Box 30)
  - [College Center] College Center Furnishings, 1972-1974 (Box 30)
  - [College Center] College Center Guarantees, 1975-1976; (5 folders) (Box 30)
  - [College Center] College Center Hardware, 1973; (3 folders) (Box 30)
  - [College Center] College Center - Housing and Urban Development, 1972-1973 (Box 30)
  - [College Center] College Center Job Meeting Minutes, 1973-1975 (Box 30)
  - [College Center] College Center Artist’s Rendering, undated (Box 30)
  - [College Center] College Center Photos, 1973-1976 (Box 30)
  - [College Center] College Center Paintings, 1973-1976 (Box 30)
  - [College Center] Prison - Fixtures College Center, 1976 (Box 30)
  - [College Center] Section 1140 Feed Service Equip., 1974; (2 folders) (Box 30)
  - [College Center] College Center Sound Module Details, 1974 (Box 30)
  - [College Center] College Center Sound System, 1975-1976; (2 folders) (Box 30)
  - [College Center] College Center Subcontractors, 1973 (Box 30)
  - [College Center] College Center Subcontractors Binghamton Steel, 1973-1975 (Box 30)
  - [College Center] College Center Transformers, 1973 (Box 30)
  - [College Center] College Center Change Orders, 1973-1974 (Box 30)
  - [College Center] College Center Change Proposals, 1973-1976 (Box 30)
  - [College Center] College Center Bids, 1973 (Box 30)
  - [College Center] Contract Award, 1970 (Box 30)
  - [College Center] Distribution Of Plans and Specs, 1973 (Box 30)
  - [College Center] Pool, 1973 (Box 30)
  - [Library - Lockwood] Library Addition Contract Documents, 1974; (3 folders) (Box 30)
  - [Library - Lockwood] Library Expansion Reports On Expenditures, 1973-1979 (Box 30)
  - [Library - Lockwood] Library Addition - Contractor Warwick Construction, Inc., 1975-1977 (Box 30)
  - [Library - Lockwood] Library Addition - K and J/ Hok Interiors, 1975-1977 (Box 30)
  - [Library - Lockwood] Library Expansion - Architect Hellmuth, Obata and Kassabaum, 1973-1978 (Box 30)
  - [Library - Lockwood] Library Expansion Wood and Tower, Inc. - Cost Consultants, 1972 (Box 31)
  - [Library - Lockwood] Library Addition - Library Consultant David Kaser, 1974 (Box 31)
  - [Library - Lockwood] Library Addition Guarantees and Warranties, 1976-1977 (Box 31)
  - [Library - Lockwood] Library Addition Job Meeting Minutes, 1974-1977 (Box 31)
  - [Library - Lockwood] Library Addition, 1975-1978 (Box 31)
  - [Library - Lockwood] Library Expansion, 1974 (Box 31)
  - [Library - Lockwood] Library Expansion - General, 1972-1974 (Box 31)
  - [Library - Lockwood] Library Addition Automatic Sprinkler Corp. Of America, 1974-1976 (Box 31)
  - [Library - Lockwood] Library Addition Borings, 1974 (Box 31)
  - [Library - Lockwood] Library Addition Furnishings, 1975-1976; (5 folders) (Box 31)
  - [Library - Lockwood] Library Addition Hardware Schedule, 1975 (Box 31)
  - [Library - Lockwood] Library Addition - Halon System, 1976-1977 (Box 31)
  - [Library - Lockwood] Library Addition Vassar College Photos, 1975-1977 (Box 31)
  - [Library - Lockwood] Library Addition Subcontractors, 1976 (Box 31)
  - [Library - Lockwood] Distribution Of Plans and Specifications, Library Addition, 1974 (Box 31)
  - [Library - Lockwood] Library Addition Change Orders, 1974-1984 (Box 31)
  - [Library - Lockwood] Library Addition Specifications, 1974 (Box 31)
  - [Library - Lockwood] Library Addition Pool, 1974; (2 folders) (Box 31)
  - [Library - Lockwood] Library Addition Shop Drawings Automatic Sprinkler Corp., 1975 (Box 31)
  - [Library - Lockwood] Library Addition Misc. Shop Drawings, 1975 (Box 31)
  - [Library - Lockwood] Library Addition Shop Drawings Sullivan County Glass Co., 1975 (Box 31)
  - [Library - Lockwood] [Kahn and Jacobs Architects, Vassar Library], 1975 (Box 32)
  - [Library - Lockwood] Library Addition Shop Drawings W. H. Kassner Inc., 1975 (Box 32)
  - [Library - Lockwood] Library Addition Shop Drawings North American Door, 1975 (Box 32)
  - [Library - Lockwood] Library Addition Shop Drawings Otis Elevator, 1975 (Box 32)
  - [Library - Lockwood] Library Addition Shop Drawings New Windsor Metal Fabricators, 1975 (Box 32)
  - [Library - Lockwood] Library Addition Shop Drawing Acme Steel Door Corporation, 1975 (Box 32)
  - [Library - Lockwood] Library Addition Shop Drawings Campbell Foundry, 1975 (Box 32)
  - [Library - Lockwood] Library Addition Shop Drawings J and G Drywall, 1975 (Box 32)
  - [Library - Lockwood] Library Addition Shop Drawings Simplex, 1975 (Box 32)
  - [Library - Lockwood] Library Addition Shop Drawings Thomas Stecklow Sons (Limestone), 1975 (Box 32)
  - [Library - Lockwood] Dir. #4 Masonry, 1975 (Box 32)
  - [Library - Lockwood] [Vassar Library Addition Drawing No. 5, Thomas Stecklow Sons], 1975 (Box 32)
  - [Library - Lockwood] Library Addition Shop Drawings Bonhag Company, 1975-1976 (Box 32)
  - [Library - Lockwood] [Vassar Library Addition Architectural Drawings], 1975 (Box 32)
  - [College Center] Section 1140 Food Service Equip. Vassar College Center Crabtree Copy, 1974-1975 (Box 32)
  - [College Center] College Center Shop Drawings Fisher Skylights Inc., 1973 (Box 32)
  - [College Center] Plumbing and Sprinkler Manuals, 1973-1975 (Box 33)
  - [College Center] College Center Electricals, 1973-1974 (Box 33)
  - [College Center] College Center H. V. A. C. Manuals, 1975 (Box 33)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] All College Dining Hall, 1972-1975 (Box 33)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Dining Facility Students’ Building Rheinstein Construction Co., Inc., 1971-1973 (Box 33)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Dining Facility Students’ Building Architect Walker O. Cain and Associates, 1970-1974 (Box 33)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Dining Facility Students’ Building Cost Consultants Wood and Tower, Inc., 1970-1971 (Box 33)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Central Dining Facility Shop Drawings, 1970-1972; (2 folders) (Box 33)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Dining Facility Students’ Building Engineers Burns and Roe, Inc., 1970-1972 (Box 33)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Central Dining Facility General, 1971-1983 (Box 33)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Dining Facilities Proposed Renovation Of Students’ Building, 1969-1971 (Box 33)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Central Dining Facility Change Orders, 1971-1974 (Box 33)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Central Dining Facility Hardware, 1973 (Box 33)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Central Dining Facility Furnishings, 1972-1973 (Box 34)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Central Dining Facility Food Service Equipment, 1972-1973; (8 folders) (Box 34)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Central Dining Facility - Transformers, 1971 (Box 34)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Central Dining Facility Job Memos, 1971-1973; (2 folders) (Box 34)
  - Job Meetings - Reports, 1971-1973 (Box 34)
  - [Utilities - Heating and Cooling] Maintenance Instructions - Electric Water Cooler Manual, 1970 (Box 34)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] [Vassar College Dining Hall Utilities], 1972 (Box 34)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Distribution Of Plans and Specifications Central Dining Facility, 1971 (Box 34)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Dining Facility (Students’ Building) Specifications, 1941 (Box 34)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Dining Facility (Students’ Building) Invitations To Bid, 1971 (Box 34)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Central Dining Facility Contract Award, 1971 (Box 34)
  - [Utilities - Heating and Cooling] H. V. A. C. Boilers, 1959-1985; (2 folders) (Box 34)
  - [Utilities - Heating and Cooling] Boiler Plant Cert, 1989 (Box 34)
  - [Utilities - Heating and Cooling] Boiler Feedwater Test Reports, 1981-1982 (Box 34)
  - [Utilities - Heating and Cooling] Specifications and Contract Documents For Repair Of Boilers, 1980 (Box 34)
  - [Utilities - Heating and Cooling] Application For Energy Conservation Measures (Projects) U. S. Department Of Energy Grant Program - For Boiler House, Vassar College, 1980 (Box 34)
  - [Utilities - Heating and Cooling] Vassar College Boiler No. 5 - Operating Instructions For Bailey Meter Company, Boiler Combustion Control System, 1979 (Box 34)
  - [Utilities - Heating and Cooling] Bailey Meter Proposal Revision To Vassar College Boiler House Controls, 1978 (Box 34)
  - [Utilities - Heating and Cooling] Vassar College Boiler No. 5 - Operating Instructions, 1981 (Box 34)
  - [Utilities - Heating and Cooling] Boiler Reports, Bailey Meter Company, 1978 (Box 34)
  - [Utilities - Heating and Cooling] Boiler House Summer Boiler, 1980 (Box 34)
  - [Utilities - Heating and Cooling] Boiler Alterations, 1976-1980 (Box 34)
  - Vassar College Buildings Report, 1942 (Box 34)
  - Buildings Areas Sizes Etc., 1967-1979 (Box 34)
  - Chalk and Bulletin Boards, 1987-1988 (Box 34)
  - [College Center] College Center, 1972-1980 (Box 34)
  - [Central Heating Plant] C. H. P., 1989 (Box 34)
  - Alan Gaynor and Company Architectural and Interior Design, 1989 (Box 34)
  - Commencement Signage, 1980-1985 (Box 34)
  - Contractors, 1988-1989 (Box 34)
  - Dorms Lofts, undated (Box 34)
  - Drawing-Drafting-Material and Prices, undated (Box 35)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Electric - 4160 V Specs and Shop Drawings, 1957-1958 (Box 35)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Electric - 4160 V - Sub Station, 1955-1956 (Box 35)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Underground Electrical Distribution System - February 3 ’85 Fault, 1985 (Box 35)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Electrical Shutdown, 1985 (Box 35)
  - Estimates, 1989-1990 (Box 35)
  - [Vassar College Farm] Farm, 1963-1987 (Box 35)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Fiber Optic/Audio Visual, 1974 (Box 35)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Fire Alarm, 1965 (Box 35)
  - Handicapped Facilities Minimum Requirements, 1961-1980; (2 folders) (Box 35)
  - [Utilities - Heating and Cooling] HVAC Faculty Houses, 1973-1981 (Box 35)
  - Handicapped Strobe, 1978 (Box 35)
  - Handicapped Elevator. Lifts Field Notes, 1978-1984 (Box 35)
  - [Utilities - Heating and Cooling] H. V. A. C. - Macon Valves, 1981 (Box 35)
  - [Utilities - Heating and Cooling] HVAC - Fuel Usage and Cost, 1973-1981 (Box 35)
  - Lettering - Simple Space-Rite, 1986-1987 (Box 35)
  - [Library - Thompson] Library “Great Window”, 1973-1976 (Box 35)
  - [Library - Thompson] Library - List Of Old Plans In ‘Special Collections’, 1969 (Box 35)
  - [Library - Thompson] Library - Rekeying, 1980 (Box 35)
  - NYS Facilities Inventory, 1971-1985; (16 folders) (Box 35)
  - CICU and Regents Progress Report Information, 1978 (Box 35)
  - Facilities Inventory and Classification Manual, 1973 (Box 35)
  - N. Y. S. Facilities Planning “Space Utilization” [Correspondence and Summaries and Worksheets], 1970 (Box 35)
  - Facilities Inventory Survey Correspondence and Summary Sheets, 1968-1971 (Box 35)
  - Facilities Inventory Summaries, 1968-1979; (3 folders) (Box 36)
  - Higher Education Data System Inventory Report, 1977 (Box 36)
  - Easements - General, 1928-1962 (Box 36)
  - Deeds (Copies From Controller’s Office), undated (Box 36)
  - Central Hudson - Easements, 1959-1968 (Box 36)
  - I. B. M. Road - Smithfield Gore, 1965-1970 (Box 36)
  - Sale Of Land Cedar Avenue To Central Hudson For Gas Regulator Station, 1969 (Box 36)
  - Poughkeepsie - (Wing Farm) Pleasant Valley Route 44-55 Connector (Lot #4 - Jewell), 1967-1969 (Box 36)
  - Easements - Richmond Hills, 1959-1960 (Box 36)
  - [Utilities - Sewer] Sewers, 1984 (Box 36)
  - Sunset Lake and Casperkill, 1968-1986 (Box 36)
  - [Skinner Hall] Skinner Hall Acoustics, 1980-1981 (Box 36)
  - Specs - Various (Brown University), 1988 (Box 36)
  - [Taylor Hall] Taylor Hall, 1953-1978 (Box 36)
  - [Taylor Hall] Taylor Art Gallery, 1989 (Box 36)
  - [Taylor Hall] Taylor Hall Addition - P. Rose, 1987-1988 (Box 36)
  - [Taylor Hall] Taylor Hall Alarm System [Security], 1971-1983 (Box 36)
  - [Athletics Facilities] Tennis Courts, 1970-1987 (Box 36)
  - N. Y. Telephone, 1957-1966 (Box 36)
  - [Library - Van Ingen] Van Ingen, 1962 (Box 36)
  - [Walker Field House] Walker FH - Chemturf FL, 1988 (Box 36)
  - [Faculty Housing] Water Faculty Houses -Vassar L. Dr. Watson, 1959-1961; (2 folders) (Box 36)
  - [Faculty Housing] 334 Hooker Ave - Murphy House, 1968 (Box 36)
  - [Olmsted Hall] Electric #1, 1972-1973 (Box 36)
  - [Olmsted Hall] Bio - Lab Job Meetings Only, 1972-1974 (Box 36)
  - [Olmsted Hall] Colors - Bio Lab, 1973 (Box 36)
  - [Olmsted Hall] Testing - Fairway, 1971-1972 (Box 36)
  - [Olmsted Hall] Bio - Lab H. U. J., 1972-1973 (Box 36)
  - [Olmsted Hall] Hardware, 1973 (Box 36)
  - [Olmsted Hall] 3 - 3B - Site Utilities, 1972-1973 (Box 36)
  - [Olmsted Hall] Architectural Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 36)
  - [Olmsted Hall] Transmittal - Letters Of Reports - Drawings. Etc. [Biological Sciences Building], 1972 (Box 36)
  - [Olmsted Hall] Misc. Items Sketches etc. [Biological Sciences Building], 1972-1973 (Box 36)
  - [Olmsted Hall] Sketches - Architectural [Biological Sciences Building], 1972-1973 (Box 37)
  - [Olmsted Hall] Primiano Correspondence [Biological Sciences Building], 1971-1972 (Box 37)
  - [Olmsted Hall] 3 - 3B - Piles Foundations [Biological Sciences Building], 1972 (Box 37)
  - [Olmsted Hall] 3 - 3A - Cast In Place Concrete [Biological Sciences Building], 1972-1973 (Box 37)
  - [Olmsted Hall] 3 - 3C - Precast Concrete Plank [Biological Sciences Building], 1972-1973 (Box 37)
  - [Olmsted Hall] 4 - 4A - Masonry [Biological Sciences Building], 1972 (Box 37)
  - [Olmsted Hall] 5 - 5A - Misc. Metals [Biological Sciences Building], 1972 (Box 37)
  - [Olmsted Hall] 5 - 5C - Access Doors [Biological Sciences Building], 1973 (Box 37)
  - [Olmsted Hall] 6 - 6A - Carpentry [Biological Sciences Building, 1973 (Box 37)
  - [Olmsted Hall] 6 - 6B - Dry Wall [Biological Sciences Building], 1972 (Box 37)
  - [Olmsted Hall] 6 - 6C - Insulation [Roof, Biological Sciences Building], 1972-1973 (Box 37)
  - [Olmsted Hall] 7 - 7A - Roofing and Flashing [Biological Sciences Building], 1972 (Box 37)
  - [Olmsted Hall] 7 - 7D - Caulking [Biological Sciences Building], 1972-1973 (Box 37)
  - [Olmsted Hall] 8 - 8A - Hollow Metal Work [Biological Sciences Building], 1972-1973 (Box 37)
  - [Olmsted Hall] 8 - 8B - Aluminum Windows Window Wall [Biological Sciences Building], 1971-1972 (Box 37)
  - [Olmsted Hall] 8 - 8D - Glass - Glazing [Biological Sciences Building], 1973 (Box 37)
  - [Olmsted Hall] 8 - 8E - Wood Doors [Biological Sciences Building], 1973 (Box 37)
  - [Olmsted Hall] 8 - 8F - Revolving Dark Room Doors [Biological Sciences Building], 1972 (Box 37)
  - [Olmsted Hall] 9 - 9B - Interior Tile [Biological Sciences Building], 1972-1973 (Box 37)
  - [Olmsted Hall] 9 - 9 F - Painting [Biological Sciences Building], 1972-1973 (Box 37)
  - [Olmsted Hall] 10 - 10A - Misc. - Fire Extinguisher’s Etc. [Biological Sciences Building], 1972 (Box 37)
  - [Olmsted Hall] 10 - 10B - Metal Toilet Partitions [Biological Sciences Building], 1972 (Box 37)
  - [Olmsted Hall] 10 - 10C - Shower Doors [Biological Sciences Building], 1972-1973 (Box 37)
  - [Olmsted Hall] 10 - 10D - Chalkboards - Tackboards [Biological Sciences Building], 1972 (Box 37)
  - [Olmsted Hall] 12 - 12A - Carpet [Biological Sciences Building], 1972-1973 (Box 37)
  - [Olmsted Hall] 13 - 13A - Skylights [Biological Sciences Building], 1973 (Box 37)
  - [Olmsted Hall] 13 - 13B - Greenhouse [Biological Sciences Building], 1972 (Box 37)
  - [Olmsted Hall] 14 - 14A - Elevators [Biological Sciences Building], 1972-1973 (Box 37)
  - [Olmsted Hall] 15 - 15C - Site Utilities [Biological Sciences Building], 1971 (Box 37)
  - [Olmsted Hall] 16 - 16AA - Fire Detection [Biological Sciences Building], undated (Box 37)
  - [Olmsted Hall] Biological Sciences Building Requisition, 1971-1973 (Box 37)
  - [Olmsted Hall] Misc. Items Biology Lab, 1974 (Box 37)
  - [Olmsted Hall] Biology Lab Paving and Correspondence, 1973 (Box 37)
  - [Olmsted Hall] Biology Lab. Hardware Schedules, 1971-1972 (Box 37)
  - [Olmsted Hall] Biology Lab Change Orders, 1971-1973 (Box 37)
  - [Olmsted Hall] 11 - 11B - Library Equipment, 1972 (Box 37)
  - [Olmsted Hall] 11 - 11A - Laboratory Equipment, 1973 (Box 37)
  - [Olmsted Hall] Addendum No. 1 To The Contract Documents For The Construction Of The Biological Sciences Building, 1971 (Box 37)
  - [Olmsted Hall] Dutchess Quarry and Supply Receipts, Biological Sciences Building, undated (Box 37)
  - [Olmsted Hall] Biological Sciences Building Plans, 1972 (Box 37)
  - [Olmsted Hall] Automatic Control System Plans, 1972 (Box 37)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] [College Dining Hall Fire Safety and Steam Tunnel Plans], 1972 (Box 37)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Dining Hall [Outdoor Utilities and Sanitation], 1973 (Box 37)
  - [Olmsted Hall] 15 - 15AA - Sprinkler [Biological Sciences Building], 1972-1973 (Box 37)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Architectural Correspondence [College Dining Hall], 1971-1972 (Box 37)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Preliminary Architectural Sketches [College Dining Hall], 1971 (Box 38)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Dining Hall - Misc. [Electrical, Plumbing and Mechanical Correspondence], 1973 (Box 38)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Glass - Glazing [College Dining Hall], 1971-1972 (Box 38)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] H. U. D. Dining Hall [Housing and Urban Development Building Inspection], 1971-1973 (Box 38)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Electrical Distribution System [College Dining Hall], 1972; (2 folders) (Box 38)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Approvals - Drawings Etc.[College Dining Hall], 1971-1972 (Box 38)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] General Notes [College Dining Hall], 1971 (Box 38)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Saddles - Gratings -Manholes [College Dining Hall folded plans], 1971 (Box 38)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] [College Dining Hall Roofing Repairs and Carpentry], 1972 (Box 38)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Benderson - Test Lab [College Dining Hall Fireproofing and Concrete Testing], 1972 (Box 38)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Concrete [Receipts and quantity forms for College Dining Hall], 1971 (Box 38)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Rolling Fire Doors and Wire Grills - North American Etc. [College Dining Hall Folded Plans], 1972 (Box 38)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Electric - O’Connor [College Dining Hall Folded Plans], 1972 (Box 38)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Food Services - Misc [College Dining Hall Folded Plans and Correspondence], 1972-1973 (Box 38)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Equipment By Vassar College, 1972 (Box 38)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Fireproofing Plastering, 1971-1972 (Box 38)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Grease / Intercenter, 1971-1972 (Box 38)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Hardware, 1971 (Box 38)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Hollow Metal Doors - Bictrite - Etc Hollow Metal Door Frames - Bictrite - Etc, 1972 (Box 38)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Insurance - Damage Claims Dining Hall, 1971 (Box 38)
  - Landscape, 1971-1973 (Box 38)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Letters Of Transmittal, 1971-1972 (Box 38)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] N. Y. S. Safety Insurance Reports, 1972; (2 folders) (Box 38)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Painting, 1972-1973 (Box 38)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] HVAC - Steam Etc, 1971-1972 (Box 38)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Procast Cone Master, 1971 (Box 38)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Piles - Wood - Steer, 1971 (Box 38)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Piling - Frank, 1971 (Box 38)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Rheinstein Const. Co., 1972 (Box 38)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Roof Screens, 1972 (Box 38)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Dining Hall Requisitions, 1972-1973 (Box 38)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Roofing E. O. Osman, 1972 (Box 38)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Specialties - Fire Ext Etc., 1971 (Box 38)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Sprinkler - Mid Hudson, 1972 (Box 38)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Job Contractors Approval, 1971-1972 (Box 38)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Skylights - E. O. Osman, 1971 (Box 38)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Toilet Fixtures Etc. Lockers, 1972 (Box 38)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Plumbing - Fox, 1971-1972 (Box 38)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Tile - Marble Etc Vinyl, 1972 (Box 38)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Telephone Chargers, 1972 (Box 38)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Wood Finish Trim, 1972 (Box 38)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Sketches - Revisions, 1971 (Box 38)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Details - Structural, 1971 (Box 38)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] HVAC - Ducts Etc. [College Dining Hall], 1971-1972 (Box 38)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Misc - Ornamental Iron, 1971 (Box 38)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Punch Lists [College Dining Hall], 1973-1974 (Box 39)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Spare Parts Receipts [College Dining Hall], 1973 (Box 39)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Old Punch Lists [College Dining Hall], 1972-1973 (Box 39)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Items By Vassar - Later Date, 1972 (Box 39)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Misc Items - Final Sketches etc. Outside Of Contracts [College Dining Hall], 1973 (Box 39)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Job Meetings - Misc. Items, 1967, 1971 (Box 39)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Masonry Modern Max, 1971 (Box 39)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Memos, 1972 (Box 39)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Misc. Architectural Correspondence [College Dining Hall], 1971 (Box 39)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Mechanical - Temperature [Fans and temperature control contract and letters of transmittal for College Dining Hall], 1971 (Box 39)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Misc. Correspondence [College Dining Hall], 1971-1972 (Box 39)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Vassar Memos [College Dining Hall], 1973 (Box 39)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Dining Hall - Arbitrations, 1971-1973 (Box 39)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Misc. Notes F. J. O., 1971 (Box 39)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Sedgwich - Elevators, 1971-1972 (Box 39)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Current [College Dining Hall], 1971-1973 (Box 39)
  - [College Center] Architectural Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 39)
  - [College Center] Addendum #1, 1973 (Box 39)
  - [College Center] Approval Sub. Contract, 1973 (Box 39)
  - [College Center] Requisitions, 1973-1975 (Box 39)
  - [College Center] Misc. Items - Reports Etc., 1973 (Box 39)
  - [College Center] Change Orders, 1973 (Box 39)
  - [College Center] Job Meeting Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 39)
  - [College Center] Engineer - Field Sketches [Lockers], 1975 (Box 39)
  - [College Center] Architectural Sketches [Transmittal Form], 1973 (Box 39)
  - [College Center] Field Sketches - F. J. O., 1973 (Box 39)
  - [College Center] Demolition, 1973 (Box 39)
  - [College Center] Excavation etc., 1973 (Box 39)
  - [College Center] Division 3 - Concrete, 1973 (Box 39)
  - [College Center] Fireproofing Products, 1974 (Box 39)
  - [College Center] Concrete Testing, 1974 (Box 39)
  - [College Center] T and M - Etc Extras [Labor and Equipment Costs], 1973-1975 (Box 39)
  - [College Center] Precast Concrete, 1974 (Box 39)
  - [College Center] Brick, 1973 (Box 39)
  - [College Center] Structural, 1973-1974 (Box 39)
  - [College Center] Metal Docking, 1973 (Box 39)
  - [College Center] Misc. Metal Architecture Orwan, 1973-1974 (Box 39)
  - [College Center] Vassar College Center Plans (Approved 2nd October 1974) (Box 39)
  - [College Center] Carpentry - Finish, 1974; (2 folders) (Box 39)
  - [College Center] Damp Proofing, 1973 (Box 39)
  - [College Center] Concrete Waterproofing, 1973 (Box 39)
  - [College Center] Moisture - Thermal Control, 1974 (Box 39)
  - [College Center] Doors - Windows - Glass, 1974 (Box 39)
  - [College Center] Finish Hardware, 1973-1975 (Box 39)
  - [College Center] Glass - Glazing, 1973 (Box 39)
  - [College Center] Metal Doors and Frames, 1973-1974 (Box 39)
  - [College Center] Wood Doors, 1974 (Box 39)
  - [College Center] [Vassar Copy - Pacific Rolling door Co. - Drawing A - 1], 1974 (Box 39)
  - [College Center] Finishes, 1974 (Box 39)
  - [College Center] Tile Work, 1973-1974 (Box 39)
  - [College Center] Acoustical Treatment, 1974 (Box 39)
  - [College Center] Painting, 1975 (Box 39)